[{"list":"Math","front":"What does Math.random() return?","back":"A pseudo-random number between 0 and 1, including 0 but excluding 1."},
{"list":"Math","front":"How can you get a pseudo-random number in JavaScript?","back":"Use the Math.random() method, which returns x, where 0<=x<1."},
{"list":"Math","front":"In JavaScript, what does `10/0` return?","back":"Infinity.  Note that JavaScript does not interpret this as an error."},
{"list":"Math","front":"Is there any possible x in Javascript such that `x!=x` evaluates true?","back":"Yes.  If x is `NaN` (not-a-number)"},
{"list":"Math","front":"In JavaScript, observe that if we run `x = .3-.2` and `y=.2-.1` then `x==y` evaluates false.  Why?  What's going on here?","back":"The problem is that numbers are represented in binary, and there is no way to represent 1/10 exactly in this scheme.  Therefore, `x==y` evaluates false because of a rounding error."},
{"list":"Syntax","front":"What are the legal identifiers in JavaScript?","back":"Must begin with a letter, _ or $.  Subsequent characters may also be numerals.  "},
{"list":"Types","front":"In JavaScript, what are the primitive types?","back":"numbers, strings, and booleans"},
{"list":"Types","front":"In JavaScript, functions are of the type: _______","back":"object.  They are objects.  "},
{"list":"Types","front":"JavaScript represents all numbers as ______","back":"64-bit floating point numbers"},
{"list":"Types","front":"In JavaScript, what is the syntax for writing a hexadecimal literal?","back":"It must start with \"0x\".  For example: \"0xCAFE911\""},
{"list":"Types","front":"In JavaScript, is the length of a string equal to the number of characters it contains?","back":"No always.  A string is an array of 16-bit values.  Most commonly used characters fit into 16 bits, but if a character does not, then it will take two (or more?) blocks.  Therefore, the length of a string could be 2 while the string only encodes 1 character."},
{"list":"Types","front":"In JavaScript, what is the syntax of a RegExp literal?","back":"`/pattern/flags` such as, for example, `/[sS]/g`"}]